<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post-punk on Tympon Musiques</title>
    <link>https://github.com/drient/tymponblog.git/genres/post-punk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post-punk on Tympon Musiques</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 09:41:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/drient/tymponblog.git/genres/post-punk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>R.J.F. - Strange Going</title>
      <link>https://github.com/drient/tymponblog.git/rjf-strange-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 09:41:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/drient/tymponblog.git/rjf-strange-going/</guid>
      <description>Description
Proud to present this debut solo outing from R.J.F. a textural patchwork of minimal melodic-inflections with room to wade in and out of. R.J.F., better known as Ross Farrar – obvious bona-fides intact – (Ceremony, Crisis Man, Spice) takes a step back from pummeling, driving front-man duties to weave ardent pieces driven by hooking lines and textures woven artfully together. Meditations on adapting lifestyles, daily-life, moving forward, stray cats looking for homes, and finding how to make sense of it all in a world always changing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course in Science - Near Marineland</title>
      <link>https://github.com/drient/tymponblog.git/near-marineland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:50:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/drient/tymponblog.git/near-marineland/</guid>
      <description>Description
Dark Entries celebrates its 15th anniversary with legendary synth-punk deviants Crash Course in Science. Dale Feliciello, Mallory Yago, and Michael Zodorozny formed CCIS in 1979 after meeting at art school in Philadelphia. As a gesture born of equal parts punk irreverence and brute necessity, the band incorporated toy instruments and kitchen appliances into their aggressive, angular sound. Their anthems “Cardboard Lamb” and “Flying Turns” from 1981’s Signals From Pier Thirteen EP have been staples in adventurous DJ sets for over 40 years - yet some of their finest work is to be found on Near Marineland, a full-length LP recorded in 1981 but remained unreleased in its time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
